Guide to the Jonathan Warner Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Realia, circa 1860-circa 1870; Series III; 0.21; (1 box)
  - Button manufactured by Evans & Co., Attleboro, Massachusetts, for a United States Army Infantry uniform, circa 1860-1865 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Eyeglasses and case with imprint for Julius King, optician, 213 Superior Street, Cleveland, Ohio, circa 1870 (Box 4, Folder 133)
- Oversize, 0.08; (1 box)
  Contains oversize material from Series II.
  - Transfer deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Jonathan Warner to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1840 February 22 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Transfer deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Jonathan Warner to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1846 January 31 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Warranty deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Joseph Addison Giddings to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1847 May 28 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Warranty deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Joseph Addison Giddings to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1849 December 3 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Warranty deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Alvin Wood and Lydia Wood to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1863 November 9 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Warranty deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Alvin Wood and Lydia Wood to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1864 April 16 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Mortgage deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Jonathan Warner, Jr., to Alvin Wood, 1864 April 19 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Mortgage deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Jonathan Warner Jr., to Alvin Wood, 1864 September 5 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Mortgage deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Stephen Hoskins to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1865 February 16 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Land contract for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from John A. Granger to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1866 November (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Warranty deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Elisha C. Pratt and Lovina C. Pratt to Jonathan Warner, 1871 September 20 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Land contract for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Jonathan Warner, Jr., to Dennis Williams, 1871 December 9 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Mortgage deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Andrew Grimes and Emily Grimes to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1876 November 23 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Mortgage of chattels for horses, wagons, and tack from Andrew Grimes to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1879 January 14 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Warranty deed for land in Denmark and Jefferson, Ohio, from Andrew Grimes and Emily Grimes to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1880 February 18 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Warranty deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Willet J. Dickinson to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1882 July 8 (Box 5, Folder 149)